<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sylvester CV</string>
    <string name="header_text">Sylvester Ranjith Francis</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Name</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_message">Message</string>
    <string name="action_submit">Send</string>
    <string name="msg_error_submitting_post">Error submitting post</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="contact_form">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_form_name">Your Name</string>
    <string name="contact_form_email">Your Email</string>
    <string name="contact_form_subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="contact_form_message">Message</string>
    <string name="contact_form_button">Send Message</string>
    <string name="contact_form_post_message">Please wait! We\'re sending your message to the support department...</string>
    <string name="contact_posted">Your message has been successfully delivered.</string>
    <string name="about_para1">The process of automating everyday tasks and making them more efficient by utilizing the computing power of a machine greatly fascinates me. Features such as recommendations of search phrases and the display of relevant product promotions based on one’s search history made me curious. The prospect of a computer actually knowing the user and responding accordingly inspired me to learn in detail about such technologies. This drove me to choose Computer Science as one of my core subjects in high school. I followed this up with an undergraduate degree in Computer Science and Engineering at Panimalar Engineering College affiliated to Anna University Chennai.</string>
    <string name="about_para2">Ever since a tender age, I have always been fascinated by the prospect of using a computer. I was introduced to computer programming at a tender age when I used BASIC to create rudimentary programs. After working on some easier computational puzzles, I wanted to delve deeper into the world of Web Dev as it afforded an opportunity for me to also fine tune my creative skills. I was inclined towards computer science engineering as the subject of study in my undergraduate as the curriculum of this course necessitated a reflection of my competencies in Programming, Analysis and Problem Solving.Having an urge to learn something new I expanded on the concepts taught in college by learning various other Programming Paradigms and Data structures. I have done a course on Python Data Structures from University of Michigan on Coursera and secured a distinction in that course.</string>
    <string name="google_plus">+SylvesterRanjithFrancis</string>
    <string name="skype">whitefire11343</string>
    <string name="whatsapp">+(91)9789084865</string>
    <string name="linkedin">www.linkedin.com/in/sylvesterranjith</string>
    <string name="twitter">whitefire00700</string>
    <string name="gmail">sylvesterranjithfrancis@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="project_title1">
      SmarterPing — Android/Web application:
   </string>
    <string name="project_description1">\n 1.  An On-the go tracking application used to track the position of delivery trucks.\n 2.  Used by Sathya Agencies to track various parameters like current speed,\n position,idling time of their delivery trucks.\n 3.  Allows the firm to maintain good customer relations by predicting the estimated time of delivery of their goods.</string>
</resources>